Behind every Olympic and Parolympic
athlete, there is a story of unwavering
dedication and sacrifice in the pursuit
of excellence. At USADA, these athletes
are our north star, and we continually
aspire to be what they deserve.
>> Every morning, we wake up before sunrise
to train.
>> Match me.
At USADA, we're going where athletes are
going with testing anywhere and anytime.
>> I watch every single thing I put in my
body to power my performance and feel
clean. Match me.
>> At USADA, we're building resources and
empowering people who help athletes
navigate prohibited substances and
methods.
I've missed holidays, birthdays, and
anniversaries to be on the field around
the world for my sport.
Match me.
>> At USADA, we're collaborating with
experts worldwide to innovate on
detection, education, and testing
methods to best serve and protect clean
athletes.
I put my body and reputation on the line
every day to be the best and do it the
right way.
Match me.
At USADA, we stand on principle to fight
for athletes rights, even when it's hard
and unpopular.
We push every day to match athletes hard
work, their pursuit of perfection, and
their commitment to excellence. Settling
isn't an option and the race isn't over.